He has the power to hear everything women are
thinking. Finally... a man is listening.
What Women Want is a comedy, romance film directed by Nancy Meyers.
Advertising executive Nick Marshall is as cocky as they come, but what happens to a
chauvinistic guy when he can suddenly hear what women are thinking?
Nick gets passed over for a promotion, but after an accident enables him to hear women's thoughts, he puts
his newfound talent to work against Darcy, his new boss, who seems to be infatuated with him.
Nick Marshall, played by Mel Gibson.
Darcy McGuire, played by Helen Hunt.
Lola, played by Marisa Tomei.
Dan Wanamaker, played by Alan Alda.
Alex Marshall, played by Ashley Johnson.
Morgan Farwell, played by Mark Feuerstein.
What Women Want is a 2000 American romantic fantasy comedy film written by Josh Goldsmith, Cathy
Yuspa, and Diane Drake, directed by Nancy Meyers, and starring Mel Gibson and Helen Hunt.
The film was released on December 15, 2000, by Paramount Pictures in the United
States and Canada and by Icon Productions in international markets.
It received mixed reviews from critics, but was a box-office success, with a North American domestic gross of $182 million and a
worldwide gross of $374.1 million against a budget of $70 million, becoming the fourth-highest-grossing film of 2000.
A loose remake, What Men Want, was released in 2019, starring Taraji P.
Henson, Tracy Morgan and Aldis Hodge.
The film explores themes of telepathy, romcom,
womanizer, single father, super power.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.